Applied and Decorative Arts Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Maps (Box 15)
  - General (Box 15)
    - Europe (Box 15)
      - Italy (Box 15)
    - North America & South America (Box 15)
      - United States (Box 15)
      - Mexico (Box 15)
  - Early Maps (Box 15)
    - Various [Slide boxes 88-89] (Box 15)
    - Peutinger Table [Slide box 89] (Box 15)
      Maps in the following sections represent the historical periods indicated
  - Pre-Historic (Box 15)
  - Primitive (Box 15)
    - Africa (Box 15)
    - North America (Box 15)
  - Pre-Columbian (Box 15)
    - Various (Box 15)
    - Andean (Box 15)
    - Mayan (Box 15)
    - Mexico [Slide box 90] (Box 15)
  - Oriental (Box 15)
    - Various (Box 15)
    - China (Box 15)
    - India (Box 15)
    - Japan (Box 15)
  - Ancient World (Box 15)
    - Near East Mesopotamian (to Babylonian Collection (Box 15)
    - Egypt (to Babylonian Collection (Box 15)
    - Aegean (Box 15)
    - Greece (Box 15)
    - Etruscan [Slide box 91] (Box 16)
    - Roman (Box 16)
  - Byzantine (Box 16)
  - Barbarian (Box 16)
  - Islamic (Box 16)
  - Medieval (Box 16)
    - Various (Box 16)
    - Trade Routes and Migrations [Slide boxes 91-92] (Box 16)
    - Near East [Slide box 92] (Box 16)
    - Europe (Box 16)
      - Various (Box 16)
      - Britain (Box 16)
      - France (Box 16)
      - Greece (Box 16)
      - Italy (Box 16)
      - Spain (Box 16)
  - Renaissance (Box 16)
    - Various (Box 16)
    - Europe (Box 16)
      - France (Box 16)
      - India (Box 16)
      - Italy (Box 16)
      - Spain (Box 16)
  - Modern Maps [Slide box 93] (Box 16)
    - Various (Box 16)
    - Europe (Box 16)
      - France (Box 16)
      - India (Box 16)
      - Italy (Box 16)
    - Latin America (Box 16)
    - United States (Box 16)
- Metals (Box 16)
  - Egypt (Box 16)
    - Various (Box 16)
  - Near East (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Various
    - Mesopotamia
    - Persia
  - Aegean (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Various
    - Funerary Masks
    - Vaphio Cups
  - Greece (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
  - Etruscan (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Various
    - Beaten Bronze Chariot Cover
    - Bronze Situla
    - Monteoleone Chariot
    - Cistae
      - Bronze Cist
      - Ficoroni Cist
    - Gold Ornaments
    - Mirrors
    - Tripods
    - Urnes
  - Roman (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Various
    - Mildenhall Treasures
  - Early Medieval [Slide box 93 cont.] (Box 16)
    - Ampullae of Monza (Box 16)
    - 4th century (Box 16)
      - Casket of Projecta and Secundus [Slide box 94] (Box 16)
      - Chalice of Antioch (Box 16)
      - Missorium of Theodosius I (Box 16)
    - 5th century (Box 16)
    - 6th century (Box 16)
    - 7th century (Box 16)
      - Various (Box 16)
      - David Plates (Box 16)
    - 8th – 9th century (Box 16)
    - 10th century (Box 16)
      - Various [Slide boxes 94-95] (Box 16)
      - Chalices [Slide box 95] (Box 16)
    - 11th century (Box 16)
      - Various (Box 16)
      - Khakhli Triptych (Box 16)
      - Pala D'Oro [Slide boxes 95-96] (Box 16)
      - S. Stephen's Crown [Slide box 96] (Box 16)
    - 12th 14th century (Box 16)
    - Barbarian (Box 16)
      - Various (Box 16)
      - Anglo-Saxon (Box 16)
        - Taplow Barrow drinking Horn (Box 16)
        - Witham Pins (Box 16)
        - Alfred Jewel (Box 16)
        - Minster Lovel Jewel (Box 16)
        - Pendants (Box 16)
        - Buckles [Slide box 97] (Box 17)
        - Sword Pommels; Hilts (Box 17)
        - Crosses (Box 17)
        - Brooches (Box 17)
          - Various (Box 17)
          - Abingdon Brooches I, II (Box 17)
          - Kingston Brooch (Box 17)
          - Sarre Brooches I, II (Box 17)
      - Sutton-Hoo Ship Burial (Box 17)
      - Large Hanging bowl (Box 17)
      - Great gold buckle (Box 17)
      - Hinged gold clasp (Box 17)
      - Iron Helmet (Box 17)
      - Purse lid (Box 17)
      - Shield and Boss [Slide boxes 97-98] (Box 17)
      - Sword Bosses and Mounts (Box 17)
      - Tremises (Box 17)
      - Whetstone Scepter (Box 17)
    - Celtic (Box 17)
      - Various (Box 17)
      - Flagons (Box 17)
      - Mirrors (Box 17)
      - Shields (Box 17)
      - Ardagh Chalice (Box 17)
      - Gundestrup Bowl (Box 17)
      - S. Patrick's Bell Shrine [Slide box 99] (Box 17)
      - Tara Brooch (Box 17)
    - Lombard (Box 17)
    - Pictish (Box 17)
    - Scandinavian (Box 17)
    - Scythian (Box 17)
      - Various (Box 17)
      - Clothing ornaments (Box 17)
      - Jewelry (Box 17)
      - Vessels (Box 17)
    - Visigothic (Box 17)
    - Merovingian [Slide box 100] (Box 17)
    - Carolingian (Box 17)
      - Altare Maggiori Milan, S. Ambrogio (Box 17)
      - Ciborium of King Arnulf (Box 17)
      - Tassilo Chalice (Box 17)
      - Reliquaries (Box 17)
        - Various (Box 17)
        - Reliquary of Enger (Box 17)
  - Austria (Box 17)
    - Various (Box 17)
    - Hoffman, Josef (Box 17)
  - Belgium (Box 17)
  - Britain (Box 17)
    - Various (Box 17)
    - 13th – 14th century (Box 17)
    - 17th century [Slide boxes 100-101] (Box 17)
    - 18th century [Slide box 101] (Box 17)
    - 19th – 20th century (Box 17)
      - Ashbee, Charles R. (Box 17)
      - Knox, Archibald (Box 17)
  - Denmark (Box 17)
  - Flanders (Box 17)
    - Various (Box 17)
    - 12th century (Box 17)
      - Stavelot Triptych (Box 17)
      - Godefroit de Huy (Box 17)
      - Nicholas of Verdun [Slide box 102] (Box 17)
        - Klosterneuberg Altarpiece (Box 17)
        - Shrine of the Virgin (Box 17)
      - Renier de Huy (Box 17)
    - 13th century (Box 17)
    - 14th century (Box 17)
  - France (Box 17)
    - 10th century (Box 17)
      - St. Foy of Conques (Box 17)
    - 11th century (Box 17)
    - 12th century (Box 17)
      - Treasury of S. Denis (Box 17)
    - 13th century (Box 17)
    - 14th century (Box 17)
    - 15th century [Slide box 103] (Box 18)
    - 16th –18th century (Box 18)
    - 19th –20th century (Box 18)
  - Germany (Box 18)
    - 10th century (Box 18)
    - 11th century (Box 18)
    - 12th century [Slide boxes 103-104] (Box 18)
      - Cologne [Slide box 104] (Box 18)
    - 13th century (Box 18)
    - 14th-15th century (Box 18)
    - 16th –17th –18th century (Box 18)
    - 19th –20th century (Box 18)
  - Greece (Box 18)
    - Various (Box 18)
  - Holland (Box 18)
    - Various (Box 18)
  - Hungary (Box 18)
    - Various (Box 18)
  - Italy (Box 18)
    - 13th century (Box 18)
    - 14th century (Box 18)
      Xx Ugolono di Vieri, Enamels Italy
    - 15th century [Slide boxes 104-105] (Box 18)
    - 16th-17th century [Slide box 105] (Box 18)
    - 19th century (Box 18)
    - 20th century (Box 18)
  - Russia (Box 18)
  - Spain (Box 18)
  - Sweden (Box 18)
  - Switzerland (Box 18)
  - Latin America (Box 18)
  - Mexico (Box 18)
  - Canada [Slide boxes 105-106] (Box 18)
  - United States (Not Pewter, Silver, or Gold) [Slide box 106] (Box 18)
    - 17th century (Box 18)
    - 18th century (Box 18)
      - Andirons (Box 18)
      - Sconces (Box 18)
    - 19th century (Box 18)
    - 20th century [Slide boxes 106-107] (Box 18)
      Xx Films U.S. In Caliente, 1935
  - U.S. Pewter [Slide box 107] (Box 18)
    - Beakers, Chalices, Flagons (Box 18)
    - Flatware, spoons (Box 18)
    - Mugs, Tankards (Box 18)
    - Pitchers (Box 18)
    - Plates, Dishes, Basins, Bowls (Box 18)
    - Porringers [Slide box 108] (Box 18)
    - Tea and Coffee Pots (Box 18)
  - U.S. Gold (Box 18)
    - Buckles (Box 18)
    - Buttons (Box 18)
    - Clasps (Box 18)
    - Teaspoons (Box 18)
  - U.S. Silver (Box 18)
    - General (Box 18)
      - 17th-18th century (Box 18)
    - Artists (Box 18)
      - A-C (Box 18)
        - Various (Box 18)
        - Coney, John [Slide boxes 108-109] (Box 18–19)
      - D-G [Slide box 109] (Box 19)
        - Various (Box 19)
        - Dummer, Jeremiah (Box 19)
          Xx Hull, Sanderson & Dummer
      - H-O (Box 19)
        - Various Artists (Box 19)
        - Hull, Sanderson & Dummer (Box 19)
        - Hurd, Jacob & Joseph [Slide boxes 109-110] (Box 19)
        - Kierstede, Cornelius [Slide box 110] (Box 19)
        - Myers, Myer (Box 19)
      - P-T (Box 19)
        - Various (Box 19)
        - Pelletreau, Elias, 1726-1810 (Box 19)
        - Potwine, John, 1698-1792 (Box 19)
        - Revere, Paul, 1735-1818 (Box 19)
        - Richardson, Joseph [Slide boxes 110-111] (Box 19)
        - Sanderson, Robert [Slide box 111] (Box 19)
        - Soumain, Samuel, 1685-1750 (Box 19)
        - Syng, Philip Jr., 1703-1789 (Box 19)
        - Ten Eyck, Jacob, 1705-1793 (Box 19)
        - Tiffany & Co. (Box 19)
      - V-Z (Box 19)
        - Various (Box 19)
        - Van der Burch, C., 1652-1699 (Box 19)
        - Van Dyck, Peter, 1684-1750 (Box 19)
        - Winslow, Edward, 1669-1753 (Box 19)
- Mosaics (Box 19)
  - Greece (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Delos
    - Pella
  - Roman (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Antioch
    - Capua Vetere
    - Herculaneum
    - Hinton St. Mary
    - Isola Sacra
    - Lullingstone Villa
    - Ostia
      - Various Titles
      - Baths of Neptune
      - Piazza delle Corporazione
    - Palestrina (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Piazza Armerina (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
      - Various Titles
      - Chamber with fishing Scene
      - Corridor Hunting Scene
      - Cubicle with Children Hunting
      - Diaeta of Arion
      - Diaeta of the Small hunting Scene
      - Gymnasium
      - Hall with the Ten Maidens
      - Triclinium
    - Pompeii (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
      - Various Titles
      - Actors before Performance
      - Amor on Tiger
      - Battle of Issos (Alexander and Darius)
      - Fish and Sealife Mosaics
      - Nile Landscape
      - Platonic Academy
      - Street Musicians
      - Woman and Sorceress
    - Qasr-El-Lebia (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Rome (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Sabratha (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Thysdrus (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Tripoli (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
    - Tunis (Transfer to Babylonian Collection, 2008)
  - Early Medieval and Renaissance [Slide box 111] (Box 19)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 111-112] (Box 19)
    - Known Sites [Slide box 112] (Box 19)
      - Aquileia (Box 19)
      - Beth Alpha (Box 19)
      - Beth Gurvin (Box 19)
      - Beth Shean (Box 19)
      - Bethlehem (Box 19)
      - Caeserea (Box 19)
      - Cefalu (Box 19)
      - Chios (Box 19)
      - Constantinople (Box 19)
        - Hagia Sophia (Box 19)
          - Apse Mosaics (Box 19)
          - Horologian Gate Lunette [Slide box 113] (Box 19)
          - Narthex Lunette (Box 19)
          - North Tympanum Mosaics (Box 19)
          - South Gallery Mosaics (Box 19)
            - Deesis Mosaic (Box 19)
            - Imperial Palace (Box 19)
        - Kariye Camii (Chora Church) (Box 19)
          - Inner Narthex (Box 19)
          - Outer Narthex (Box 19)
          - Nave [Slide box 114] (Box 19)
        - S. Mary Panmakaristos (Box 19)
      - Corinth (Box 19)
      - Damascus (Box 19)
      - Daphni (Box 19)
      - Ein Gedi (Box 19)
      - Florence (Box 19)
      - Gaza (Box 19)
      - Gerasa (Box 19)
      - Germingny-Des-Pres (Box 19)
      - Grottoferrata (Box 19)
      - Hammath Tiberius (Box 19)
      - Hippo (Box 19)
      - Hosios Loukas (Box 19)
      - Jerusalem (Box 19)
      - Khirbet Es-Samra [Slide box 115] (Box 20)
      - Kiev (Box 20)
      - Kissufim, Israel (Box 20)
      - Kiti, Cyprus (Box 20)
      - Lithrankomi, Cyprus (Box 20)
      - Madaba (Box 20)
        Xx for Mosaic map of Jerusalem, see arch. Early Medieval Jerusalem
      - Ma'in, Jordan (Box 20)
      - Milan (Box 20)
      - Monreale (Box 20)
        - Apse (Box 20)
        - Nave [Slide boxes 115-116] (Box 20)
        - Transept [Slide box 116] (Box 20)
      - Mount Nero (Box 20)
      - Mount Nero (Box 20)
      - Mount Sinai (Box 20)
      - Naples (Box 20)
      - Norton Priory (Box 20)
      - Palermo (Box 20)
        - Various Titles (Box 20)
        - Capella Palatina (Box 20)
        - La Martorana (Box 20)
      - Pisa (Box 20)
      - Ravello (Box 20)
      - Ravenna (Box 20)
        - Various Titles (Box 20)
        - Archepiscopal Palace (Box 20)
        - Arian Baptistry (Box 20)
        - Baptistry of the Orthodox (Box 20)
        - S. Apollinare in Classe [Slide box 117] (Box 20)
          - Various titles (Box 20)
          - Apse (Box 20)
          - Presbyterium (Box 20)
          - Triumphal Arch (Box 20)
        - S. Apollinare Nuovo (Box 20)
          - Various Titles (Box 20)
          - Nave (Box 20)
        - S. Vitale (Box 20)
          - Various Titles (Box 20)
          - Arch (Box 20)
          - Presbytery [Slide boxes 117-118] (Box 20)
            - Presbytery Vault (Box 20)
            - Justinian and Retinue [Slide box 118] (Box 20)
            - Theodora and Retinue (Box 20)
          - Tomb of Galla Placida (Box 20)
      - Rome (Box 20)
        - Various Titles (Box 20)
        - Mausoleum of the Julii (Box 20)
        - Oratory of John VII (Box 20)
        - S. Agnese f.1.m. (Box 20)
        - S. Clemente (Box 20)
          - Scroll details (apse) (Box 20)
        - S. Constanza [Slide box 119] (Box 20)
        - S. Cosmas and Damian (Box 20)
        - S. Giovanni Laterano (Box 20)
        - S. Lorenzo f.1.m. (Box 20)
        - S. Maria in Ara Celi (Box 20)
        - S. Maria in Domnica (Box 20)
        - S. Maria Maggiore (Box 20)
          - Various Titles (Box 20)
          - Nave (Box 20)
          - Triumphal Arch (Box 20)
        - S. Maria Trastevere (Box 20)
        - S. Paolo Fuori Le Mura [Slide box 120] (Box 20)
        - S. Peter's (Box 20)
        - S. Prassede (Box 20)
        - S. Pudenziana (Box 20)
        - S. Stefano Rotundo (Box 20)
      - S. Denis (Box 20)
      - Salonika (Box 20)
        - Various Titles (Box 20)
        - Hagia Georgios (Box 20)
        - Hosios David (Box 20)
        - S. Demetrios (Box 20)
      - Sepphoris (Box 20)
      - Torcello (Box 20)
        - Cathedral (Box 20)
          - Altar (Box 20)
          - Apse (Box 20)
          - West Wall [Slide boxes 120-121] (Box 20–21)
      - Um Er-Rasas, Jordan [Slide box 121] (Box 21)
      - Venice (Box 21)
        - S. Marco (Box 21)
          - Façade Mosaics (Box 21)
            - Atrium (Box 21)
              - Creation Dome (Box 21)
              - Abraham Dome (Box 21)
              - Joseph I Dome (Box 21)
              - Joseph II Dome (Box 21)
              - Joseph III Dome (Box 21)
              - Moses Dome (Box 21)
              - Story of Noah (Box 21)
            - Apse (Box 21)
              - Various (Box 21)
              - Apser: Dome (Box 21)
            - Baptistry (Box 21)
            - Chapels [Slide box 121] (Box 21)
              - Various Chapels (Box 21)
              - Cappella dei Mascoli (Box 21)
              - Cappella S. Pietro (Box 21)
            - Nave (Box 21)
              - Entry into Jerusalem (Box 21)
              - Agony in the Garden (Box 21)
              - Betrayal & Mocking (Box 21)
              - Crucifixion (Box 21)
              - Anastasis (Box 21)
              - Ascension Dome (Box 21)
              - Pentecost Dome (Box 21)
            - Left Transept (Box 21)
            - Right Transept (Box 21)
    - 19th- 20th century (Box 21)
      - Various (Box 21)
      - France (Box 21)
      - Italy [Slide boxes 122-123] (Box 21)
      - Russia [Slide box 123] (Box 21)
      - Spain (Box 21)
- Medals (Box 21)
  - Italy (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Bernardi (Box 21)
    - Boldu, Giovanni, ac. 1454-1477 (Box 21)
    - Clemente da Urbino (Box 21)
    - Fiorentino, Adriano (Box 21)
    - Francesco di Giorgio (Box 21)
    - Gambello, Vittone (Box 21)
    - Guacioloti, Andrea (Box 21)
    - Leoni, Leone (Box 21)
    - Melioli, Bartolommeo (Box 21)
    - Niccolo Fiorentino [Slide boxes 123-124] (Box 21)
    - Pasti, Matteodi Andrea de [Slide box 124] (Box 21)
    - Pisanello (Box 21)
    - Serbaldi da Pescia (Box 21)
    - Sperandio, Savelli (Box 21)
  - United States (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
- Stage Design (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - Austria (Box 21)
    - Hakart, Hans, 1840-1884 (Box 21)
  - Britain (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Hockney, David, 1937- (Box 21)
    - Jones, Inigo, 1573-1652 [Slide boxes 124-125] (Box 21)
  - France [Slide box 125] (Box 21)
    - Leger, Fernand (Box 21)
  - Germany (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Grosz, George, 1893-1905 (Box 21)
    - Schinkel, K.F. (Box 21)
    - Schlemmer, Oskar, 1888-1943 (Box 21)
    - Schmidt, Kurt (Box 21)
    - Schwitters, K., 1887-1948 (Box 21)
  - Hungary (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo [Slide box 126] (Box 21)
  - Italy (Box 21)
    - Parigi, Giulio (Box 21)
  - Russia (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21)
    - Delaunay, Sonia, 1885-1979 (Box 21)
    - Eisenstein, Sergei (Box 21)
    - Exter, Alexandra, 1884-1949 (Box 21)
    - Lissitsky, El, 1840-1941 (Box 21)
    - Malevich, Kasimir, 1878-1949 (Box 21)
    - Popova, Liubov, 1889-1924 (Box 21)
    - Shestakov, Varvara, 1894-1958 [Slide box 127] (Box 22)
    - Tatlin, Vladimir, 1885-1953 (Box 22)
    - Vesnin, Alexander, 1883-1953 (Box 22)
    - Yakulov, Alesandr, d.1938 (Box 22)
  - Spain (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 1881-1973 (Box 22)
  - United States (Box 22)
    - Cambria, Frank (Box 22)
    - Geddes, Norman Bel (Box 22)
    - Noguchi, Isamu, 1904- (Box 22)
    - Porgy & Bess (Box 22)
    - Salle, David, 1952- [Slide box 128] (Box 22)
    - Stettheimer, Florine, 1871-1944 (Box 22)
    - Wiley, William, 1937- (Box 22)
- Musical Instruments (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Italy (Box 22)
  - Spain (Box 22)
  - United States (Box 22)
- Numismatics (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Celtic (Box 22)
  - Scandinavian (Box 22)
  - Early Medieval (Box 22)
  - France (Box 22)
  - Italy (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Cellini (Box 22)
  - Spain (Box 22)
  - United States (Box 22)
- Rugs (Box 22)
  - Morocco (Box 22)
  - United States (Box 22)
- Seals (Box 22)
  - France (Box 22)
  - Germany (Box 22)
  - Italy (Box 22)
  - United States (Box 22)
- Stained Glass (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
  - Techniques (Box 22)
  - Britain [Slide box 129] (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
      - Canterbury Cathedral (Box 22)
      - Eaton Bishop (Box 22)
      - Wells Cathedral (Box 22)
      - York Minster (Box 22)
    - Known artists (Box 22)
      - Various (Box 22)
      - Burne-Jones, Edward, 1833-1898 (Box 22)
      - Rossetti, Dante Gabriel, 1828-1882 (Box 22)
      - William Morris & Co. (Box 22)
  - Flanders (Box 22)
  - France (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 22)
      - Various (Box 22)
      - Amiens (Box 22)
      - Angers (Box 22)
      - Auxterre (Box 22)
      - Bourges (Box 22)
      - Chartres (Box 22)
        - Ambulatory [Slide boxes 19-130] (Box 22)
        - Nave [Slide box 130] (Box 22)
        - West Facade (Box 22)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
          - Center lancet (Box 22)
          - South lancet (left) (Box 22)
      - North Transept (Box 22)
      - South Transept [Slide box 131] (Box 22)
        - St. Denis Window (Box 22)
    - Chemille sur Andois (Box 22)
    - Clermont Ferrand (Box 22)
    - Le Cham in Iserve (Box 22)
    - Le Mans (Box 22)
    - Paris (Box 22)
    - Poitiers (Box 22)
    - St. Remi (Box 22)
    - Rheims (Box 22)
    - Rouen (Box 22)
    - S. Denis (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
      - Life of Moses (Box 22)
    - Strassbourg (Box 22)
    - Tours (Box 22)
    - Troyes (Box 22)
    - 20th century (Box 22)
      - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 22)
      - Arp, Hans (Box 22)
      - Leger, Fernand (Box 22)
      - Matisse, Henri [Slide box 132] (Box 22)
  - Germany (Box 22)
  - Holland (Box 22)
  - Italy (Box 22)
  - Switzerland (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
      - Lausanne Cathedral (Box 22)
  - United States (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - La Farge, John, 1835-1910 (Box 22)
    - Tiffany, Louis C., 1848-1933 (Box 22)
- Tapestry (Box 22)
  - Britain (Box 22)
  - Flanders (Box 22)
  - France [Slide box 133] (Box 23)
    - Bayeux Tapestry (Box 23)
      - Bayeux Tapestry (Box 23)
        - 1-10 (Box 23)
        - 11-20 (Box 23)
        - 21-30 (Box 23)
        - 31-40 (Box 23)
        - 41-50 (Box 23)
        - 51-60 (Box 23)
      - 14th century (Box 23)
        - Angers Apocalypse (Box 23)
        - Nine Heroes (Box 23)
      - 15th century (Box 23)
        - Lady and the Unicorn (Box 23)
        - Unicorn Tapestries (Box 23)
      - 16th century (Box 23)
      - 17th century (Box 23)
      - 20th century (Box 23)
        - Miscellaneous artists (Box 23)
        - Le Corbusier (Box 23)
        - Ranson, Paul (Box 23)
        - Simon, Lucien (Box 23)
  - Germany (Box 23)
  - Italy (Box 23)
  - Norway (Box 23)
  - Spain (Box 23)
  - Switzerland (Box 23)
  - United States (Box 23)
- Textiles (Box 23)
  - Egypt, Coptic [Slide boxes 134-135] (Box 23)
  - Near East (Box 23)
  - Austria (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous Artists (Box 23)
    - Hoffman, Joseff, 1870-1956 (Box 23)
    - Klimt, Gustave, 1862-1918 (Box 23)
    - Moser, Kolo, 1868-1918 (Box 23)
    - Schiele, Egon, 1890-1918 (Box 23)
    - Wiener Werkstatte (Box 23)
  - Belgium (Box 23)
    - Velde, Henri van der (Box 23)
  - Britain (Box 23)
    - S. Cuthbert's Coffin (Box 23)
    - 19th – 20th centuries [Slide box 136] (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
      - Burne-Jones, Edward (Box 23)
      - Mackintosh, C.R. (Box 23)
      - Morris, William (Box 23)
  - Finland (Box 23)
  - France (Box 23)
  - Germany (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Behrens, Peter (Box 23)
    - Bauhaus textiles (Box 23)
    - Riemerschmid, R. (Box 23)
  - India (Box 23)
  - Italy (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Fortuny, Mariano, 1871-1949 (Box 23)
    - Pollaiuolo, Antonio, 1433-1498 (Box 23)
  - Russia (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Delaunay, Sonia, 1885-1979 (Box 23)
    - Kandinsky, Wassily, 1866-1944 (Box 23)
    - Popova, Liubov, 1889-1924 (Box 23)
    - Stepanova, Varvara, 1894-1958 (Box 23)
  - Spain (Box 23)
  - Switzerland [Slide boxes 137-138] (Box 23)
  - Latin America [Slide box 138] (Box 23)
  - United States (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Costume (Box 23)
    - Coverlets & bedspreads (Box 23)
    - Quilts [Slide boxes 138-139] (Box 23–24)
    - 20th century [Slide box 139] (Box 23–24)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 23–24)
      - Albers, Anni (Box 23–24)
      - Karasz, Ilonka, 1896-1981 (Box 23–24)
      - Reeves, Ruth, 1892-1966 (Box 23–24)
      - Sheeler, Charles, 1883-1965 (Box 23–24)
      - Zorach, Marguerite, 1888- (Box 23–24)
- Wallpaper (Box 23–24)
  - Britain (Box 23–24)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23–24)
    - Morris, William [Slide boxes 139-140-141] (Box 24)
  - France [Slide box 141] (Box 24)
  - Germany (Box 24)
  - United States (Box 24)
- Wood carving (Box 24)
  - Britain (Box 24)
    - Gibbons, Grinling (Box 24)
  - Germany (Box 24)
  - Italy (Box 24)
  - Spain (Box 24)